ANSIETUNG UX DESIGNER

New York, NY

(917) 770 - 3702

in www.linkedin.com/in/annie-xiu

www.annietung.design

PROJECTS

Inkspire | iOS Prototype

Researcher, UX and UI Designer

Designed for iPhone, Inkspire is an app for tattoo enthusiasts. It is an all-in-one app to find inspiration, find the right artist for you, and at any location. Additional functions include saving images to your personal profile, messaging, and scheduling appointments.

Flashcheck | iOS Prototype

Researcher, UX and UI Designer

Designed for iPhone, Flashcheck is a flashcard app that helps you study and memorize vocabulary more efficiently. Users can create their own deck or find pre-made decks from other users in the community.

EXPERIENCE

Sarku Japan, Elizabeth, NJ

Assistant Manager

Jan 2020 - Oct 2021

- Designed and oversaw the infrastructure to encourage social distancing and Covid-19 safety protocols
- Monitored inventory of supplies and negotiated with suppliers saving up to 20% in cost
- Maintained records and prepared staff schedules for 11 employees

ABI Care Inc, Queens, NY

Elderly Caregiver

Feb 2019 - Sept 2020

• Assisted clients with personal care, administered medications, light house keeping duties, and improving quality of life by responding to all physical and emotional needs

Planned Parenthood, NYC,NY

Health Educator

Feb 2014 - Sept 2017

- Addressed clients' concerns about sexual health with quality and empathetic approach for young adolescents to older adults
- Helped clients learn how to make informed health decisions for their next course of action

Suffolk University, Boston, MA Research Assistant

Jan 2011 - Feb 2012

- Assisted research in conducting experiments in both controlled and experimental settings with over 600 participants to determine how consumption of media affects child development.
- Contribute to research including recruiting, interviewing, briefing, and debriefing participants, literature search, and data entry for analysis using SPSS.

ABOUT ME

I'm a UX Designer with a background in research and mental health. My experience as a researcher honed my data gathering and analysis skills while applying my knowledge of human behavior and cognitive processes through empathetic interpersonal interactions.

I studied UX design and received weekly mentorship through CareerFoundry design program.

EDUCATION

CareerFoundry UX Design Program

2019-2020 | UX Design and Frontend Development Specialization

Suffolk University, MA

2009-2012 | BS Psychology GPA: 3.23

SKILLS

Information Architecture

User Personas

User Interviews

Competitive Analysis

Prototyping

Wireframing

Journey Mapping

User research

Usability Testing

Preference Testing

A/B Testing

Usability Analysis

LANGUAGE

HTML (basic) and CSS (basic) English and Mandarin (Fluent)

TOOLS

Adobe XD Sketch

Figma

Miro